[{"question":"What buff does Braun Strowman \"Monster Among Men\" give as a trainer?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Protect Gems Reduce Damage taken by an additional {x}%."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Blue Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Black Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Yellow Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."}]},{"question":"What buff does Bobby Roode \"The Glorious One\" give as a trainer?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Take {x}% less Damage from Black Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Yellow Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Yellow Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Yellow Gems do {x}% more Damage."}]},{"question":"What buff does Big Show \"The World's Largest Athlete\" give as a trainer?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Purple Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Purple Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Yellow Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Blue Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."}]},{"question":"What buff does Big E \"The New Day\" give as a trainer?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Yellow Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Multiply Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Blue Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take {x}% less Damage from Black Moves."}]},{"question":"What buff does Big Cass \"Certified G\" give as a trainer?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Blue Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take {x}% less Damage from Black Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Blue Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Red Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."}]},{"question":"What buff does Big Boss Man \"Hard Times\" give as a trainer?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Multiply Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Blue Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take {x}% less Damage from Black Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Black Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."}]},{"question":"What buff does Batista \"The Animal\" give as a trainer?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Red Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Black Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Red Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Red Gems do {x}% more Damage."}]},{"question":"What buff does Andre The Giant \"Eighth Wonder of the World\" give as a trainer?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Purple Gems do {x} more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Multiply Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Purple Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Green Gems do {x}% more Damage."}]},{"question":"What buff does Bam Bam Bigelow \"The Beast from the East\" give as a trainer?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Multiply Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive {x}% less Damage from Purple Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Black Moves Deal {x}% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take {x}% less Damage from Black Moves."}]},{"question":"How many \"Winged Shoes\" does it take to evolve a Acrobat from 3SB to 3SS?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"40"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"35"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"30"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"25"}]},{"question":"How many \"Winged Shoes\" does it take to evolve a Acrobat from 2SG to 3SB?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"30"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"25"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"20"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"15"}]},{"question":"How many \"Winged Shoes\" does it take to evolve a Acrobat from 2SS to 2SG?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"20"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"15"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"10"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"25"}]},{"question":"How many \"Winged Shoes\" does it take to evolve a Acrobat from 2SB to 2SS?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"15"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"10"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"20"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"5"}]},{"question":"How many \"Winged Shoes\" does it take to evolve a Acrobat from 1SG to 2SB?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"10"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"15"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"5"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"2"}]},{"question":"How many \"Winged Shoes\" does it take to evolve a Acrobat from 1SS to 1SG?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"5"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"7"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"10"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"2"}]},{"question":"How many \"Winged Shoes\" does it take to evolve a Acrobat from 1SB to 1SS?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"0"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"2"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"4"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"3"}]},{"question":"How many \"Microphones\" does it take to evolve a Showboat from 3SB to 3SS?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"50"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"55"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"45"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"40"}]},{"question":"How many \"Microphones\" does it take to evolve a Showboat from 2SG to 3SB?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"40"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"35"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"30"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"45"}]},{"question":"How many \"Microphones\" does it take to evolve a Showboat from 2SS to 2SG?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"30"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"20"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"35"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"25"}]},{"question":"How many \"Microphones\" does it take to evolve a Showboat from 2SB to 2SS?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"20"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"15"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"10"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"25"}]},{"question":"How many \"Microphones\" does it take to evolve a Showboat from 1SG to 2SB?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"15"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"10"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"20"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"12"}]},{"question":"What tag team buff does \"Nexus\" link give?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Receive 40% less Damage from Black Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 60% less Damage from Yellow Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Gems do 5% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Gems do 10% more Damage."}]},{"question":"What tag team buff does \"The Corporation\" link give?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Take 60% less Damage from Yellow Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 40% less Damage from Red Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 30% less Damage from Green Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Gems do 10% more Damage."}]},{"question":"What tag team buff does \"The Authority\" link give?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Take 40% less Damage from Red Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 30% less Damage from Green Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 60% less Damage from Yellow Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive 40% less Damage from Black Gems."}]},{"question":"What tag team buff does \"The Wyatt Family\" link give?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Take 30% less Damage from Green Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Gems do 5% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 60% less Damage from Green Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 40% less Damage from Red Moves."}]},{"question":"What tag team buff does \"Brothers of Destruction\" link give?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Take 60% less Damage from Green Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 40% less Damage from Red Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Gems do 5% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive 40% less Damage from Black Gems."}]},{"question":"What tag team buff does \"Modern Era\" link give?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Gems do 5% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 60% less Damage from Yellow Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive 40% less Damage from Black Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 30% less Damage from Green Moves."}]},{"question":"What tag team buff does \"New Generation\" link give?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Gems do 10% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 30% less Damage from Green Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 60% less Damage from Green Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive 40% less Damage from Black Gems."}]},{"question":"What tag team buff does \"Legends Era\" link give?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Gems do 10% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Gems do 15% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 30% less Damage from Green Moves."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Take 40% less Damage from Red Moves."}]},{"question":"What is the reward for achieving 300 Fame Points in VS?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"1000 x Coins"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1 x Mystery TP 3 Bag"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1 x Back Support"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"2000 x Coins"}]},{"question":"What is the reward for achieving 100 Fame Points in VS?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"200 x Coins"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1 x Regal Mandate"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1 x Mystery 1 TP Bag"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"500 x Coins"}]},{"question":"How much Notoriety in VS. is needed to stay in \"Lightweight League I\"?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"700 - 799"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"500 - 599"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"600 - 699"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"350 - 399"}]},{"question":"How much Notoriety in VS. is needed to stay in \"Lightweight League II\"?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"600 - 699"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"350 - 399"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"400 - 449"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"500 - 599"}]},{"question":"How much Notoriety in VS. is needed to stay in \"Lightweight League III\"?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"500 - 599"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"700 - 799"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"400 - 449"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"350 - 399"}]},{"question":"How much Notoriety in VS. is needed to stay in \"Professional League I\"?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"450 - 499"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"300 - 349"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"350 - 399"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"800 - 999"}]},{"question":"How much Notoriety in VS. is needed to stay in \"Professional League II\"?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"400 - 449"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"700 - 799"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"350 - 399"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"300 - 349"}]},{"question":"How much Notoriety in VS. is needed to stay in \"Professional League III\"?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"350 - 399"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"400 - 449"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"600 - 699"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"800 - 999"}]},{"question":"How much Notoriety in VS. is needed to stay in \"Regional League I\"?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"300 - 349"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"350 - 399"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"500 - 599"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"800 - 999"}]},{"question":"How much Notoriety in VS. is needed to stay in \"Regional League II\"?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"250 - 299"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"300 - 349"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"600 - 699"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"800 - 999"}]},{"question":"How much Notoriety in VS. is needed to stay in \"Regional League III\"?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"200 - 249"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"600 - 699"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1200 - 1399"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"450 - 499"}]},{"question":"What class is Big Boss Man “Hard Times”?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Striker Aggressive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Striker Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Striker Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Striker Focused"}]},{"question":"What class is Batista “The Animal”?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Powerhouse Aggressive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Powerhouse Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Powerhouse Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Powerhouse Focused"}]},{"question":"What class is Baron Corbin “The Lone Wolf”?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Striker Aggressive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Striker Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Striker Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Striker Focused"}]},{"question":"What class is Bam Bam Bigelow “The Beast from the East”?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Powerhouse Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Powerhouse Focused"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Powerhouse Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Powerhouse Aggressive"}]},{"question":"What class is Arn Anderson “Double A”?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Trickster Focused"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Trickster Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Trickster Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Trickster Aggressive"}]},{"question":"What class is Andre The Giant “Eighth Wonder of the World”?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Trickster Aggressive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Trickster Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Trickster Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Trickster Focused"}]},{"question":"What class is Andre The Giant “Irresistible Force”?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Showboat Aggressive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Showboat Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Showboat Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Showboat Focused"}]},{"question":"What class is Alberto Del Rio “The Pride of Mexico”?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Technician Focused"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Technician Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Technician Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Technician Aggressive"}]},{"question":"What class is AJ Styles “The Possessed One”?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Showboat Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Showboat Aggressive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Showboat Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Showboat Focused"}]},{"question":"What class is AJ Styles “The Phenomenal One”?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Acrobat Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Acrobat Aggressive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Acrobat Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Acrobat Focused"}]},{"question":"What buff does Baron Corbin “The Lone Wolf” give as a trainer?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Receive x% less Damage from Purple Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive x% less Damage from Multiply Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Black Moves Deal 5% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Red Moves Deal 5% more Damage."}]},{"question":"What tag team buff does \"Heenan Family\" link give?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Receive 60% less Damage from Blue Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Receive 60% less Damage from Yellow Gems."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Gems do 15% more Damage."},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Immobile Gems do 50% more Damage."}]},{"question":"Which of the following Superstars does NOT have a Legend tag buff?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Bam Bam Bigelow \"The Beast From The East\""},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Ric Flair \"The Nature Boy\""},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Honky Tonk Man \"Shake, Rattle, and Roll\""},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Jerry Lawler \"The King\""}]},{"question":"What is the reward for achieving 400 Fame Points in VS?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"1 x Mystery TP 3 Bag"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1000 x Coins"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"2000 x Coins"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1 x Standard Toolbox"}]},{"question":"What is the reward for achieving 200 Fame Points in VS?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"500 x Coins"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1 x Mystery TP 3 Bag"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1 x Built in a Day"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1 x Standard Toolbox"}]},{"question":"What is the reward for \"NXT Tour - Atlanta - Node 1\"?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Coins x5000"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Coins x4000"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Coins x3000"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Coins x6000"}]},{"question":"How many \"Microphones\" does it take to evolve a Showboat from 1SS to 1SG?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"10"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"5"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"15"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"8"}]},{"question":"How many \"Microphones\" does it take to evolve a Showboat from 1SB to 1SS?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"5"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"10"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"2"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"8"}]},{"question":"What class is Steve Austin “The Texas Revenant”","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Powerhouse Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Powerhouse Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Powerhouse Aggressive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Powerhouse Focused"}]},{"question":"What class is John Cena “Hustle, Loyalty, Respect”?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Showboat Aggressive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Showboat Chaotic"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Showboat Defensive"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Showboat Focused"}]},{"question":"You just evolved Enzo from 3* bronze to 3*silver. How much gold would it take to max his levels (lv. 80-100)","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"2.4 million"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1.2 million"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"1.4 million"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"2.1 million"}]},{"question":"How much does each level cost if your Superstar is 3* bronze?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"120,000"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"100,000"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"140,000"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"240,000"}]},{"question":"Outside of Blitz or Feud events, who can you NOT post for faction heal requests?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"3* Silver Enzo"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"3* Gold Mark Henry"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"3* Gold Big Show"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"3* Bronze Stardust"}]},{"question":"You just kicked out of a pin, your opponent is in danger and has no health left. What is the minimum amount of gems you need to break to pin your opponent and win?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"6"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"5"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"7"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"8"}]},{"question":"You just kicked out of a pin, your opponent has health left. What is the minimum amount of gems you need to break to pin your opponent?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"11"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"10"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"12"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"13"}]},{"question":"If the upcoming Faction Feud requirements are: 2 Legends, 2 Raw Power Houses, 1 Raw Striker. Select the superstar below that CANNOT be posted for faction heal requests during the feud.","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Doink The Clown “The Prankster”"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Bray Wyatt “The Eater of Worlds”"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Andre The Giant “Irresistible Force”"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Titus O'Neil “Prime Time Players”"}]},{"question":"When helping your teammates, always heal ______","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"From the top first, then work your way down"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"From the bottom first, then work your way up"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Anyone you can quickly see on your screen so you can get back into the next feud ASAP"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Only when you need heals yourself"}]},{"question":"What is the goal for Faction Feuds?","answers":[{"isCorrect":true,"text":"Score as many points as possible, as efficiently as possible, while working together as a team"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"If outmatched, use props to help ensure a victory"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Work hard and fast to score as many points as you personally can"},{"isCorrect":false,"text":"Beat your opponent at all costs"}]}]